Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Posters and Oversized Materials, 1948-2018, undated
  • Oversized Material (Box 164 and oversized) includes advertisements, clippings, and mounted photographs, clippings, advertisements and is arranged alphabetically by artist. The majority of the material is housed in the map cases.
  - Artist Posters - Male
    - Ace & Co. - Johnny Bustamante and L.A. Boys, 1990, 2004, undated (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Johnny Canales - Culturas, 1984, undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Dee y Grupo Valiente - La Fuerza, 1989, 1996, undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Oscar G. - Salomé Gutierrez, circa 1978, 1989, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - La Herencia Chicana - Karloz, 1987,1996, 2000, undated (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Liberty Band - Jorge Moreno, 1987, 2010, 2016, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Emilio Navaira - Marcos Orozco, 1990, undated (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Los Paisanos - Roberto Pulido y Los Clasicos, 1982, 1999, undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Ralph and The Cruisers - The Royal [6?], 1996, 2000, undated (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Michael Salgado - Sunny & the Sunliners, 1995-1996, 1999, undated (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Los Tall Boys de Johnny Mora - Tortilla Factory, 1987, 1993, 1997, 2002, undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - La Traizon - The Twin City Band, 1988, undated (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Roger Velasquez - Pedro Yerena, 2013, 2016, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Various Artists, 1981, 1991, 1996, 2008, undated (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Various Artists. Mounted publicity photographs, album covers (including a signed cover of Andan Diciendo), and wall text from Hernandez's exhibit on Los Guadalupanos (also includes Mingo Salidavar, Los Aguilares, Carlos Miranda, and others), undated (Box 158)
    - Male Artist Oversize Mounted Posters. Johnny Hernandez - "Los Tres Amigos", September 1988, undated (Box 159)
  - Artist Posters - Female Artists
    - Agnes y Arturo - Norma Eliza, 2004, undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Linda Escobar - Letty Guval, 1968, 1989, 2004, 2006, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Tish Hinojosa - Lizza, 1984, 1987, 1990, 2005, undated (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Beatriz Llamas, 1982, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Mari Lou - Nydia Rojas, 1999, 2005, undated (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Roxanne - Stefani [Montiel], 1995, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Tejano Roze y La Nueva Sensacion - Rita Vidaurri, 1986, 1999, 2002, undated (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - Female Artists Oversized Mounted Posters. Laura Canales - Patsy Torres, 1990, 1992, 1994, undated (Box 161)
  - Oversized Posters - Male Artists
    - Adalberto - Ramon Ayala, 1996, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 1)
    - Bandango - Johnny Bustamente, 1994, 1997, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 2)
    - Campanas de America - Micky Cruz, 1999, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 3)
    - DaHeBeGeBees - Los Dos Gilbertos, 1965, 1990-1991, 1996, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 4)
    - Estrella - Eterno, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 5)
    - Fama - La Franz, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 6)
    - Los Galanes - Tony Guerro Orchestra, 1996, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 7)
    - Little Joe Hernandez, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 8)
    - Johnny Hernandez - Gary Hobbs, 1988-1989, 1995, 1997, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 9)
    - Jaime y Los Chamacos - Kumbia Kings, 1987, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 10)
    - Latin Image - Gabe Lopez and the System, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 11)
    - La Mafia, 1995-1999, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 12)
    - David Marez - Juan P. Moreno, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 13)
    - Emilio Navaira, 1991, 1993, 1997, 2001, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 14)
    - Los Palominos - El Privilegio, 1996, 1983, 1997, 2006, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 15)
    - Augustin Ramirez - Rodeo, 1994, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 16)
    - Michael Salgado - La Sombra, 1995, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 17)
    - Texas Express - La Tropa F, 1985, 1992, 1994, 1996, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 18)
    - Uptown Band - Henry Zimmerle, 1992, 2000, undated (Map-case 36, Folder 19)
  - Oversized Posters - Female Artists
    - Arturo y Agnes New Variety Band - Culturas, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 1)
    - Elida y Avante - Letty Guval, 1993, 1994-1995, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 2)
    - Jennifer y Los Jetz - Stephanie Lynn & High Energy, 1991-1992, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 3)
    - Margarita - Anna Roman, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Jaci Velásquez, 1995, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 5)
  - Concert Posters
    - 1948-1993 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - 1997-2010 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - 2011-2017 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - February-June [no year] (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - July-December [no year] (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Advertisements, 1981-2001, undated (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - Mounted Concert Posters and Artwork, 1999, undated (Box 163)
  - Oversized Concert Posters
    - 1957-1991 (Map-case 37, Folder 6)
    - 1992 (Map-case 37, Folder 7)
    - 1993-1994 (Map-case 37, Folder 8)
    - 1995-1999 (Map-case 37, Folder 9)
    - 2001-2015 (Map-case 37, Folder 10)
    - February-October [no year] (Map-case 37, Folder 11)
  - Clippings
    - Little Joe Hernandez, 1981-1989 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Little Joe Hernandez, 1990-1999 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Little Joe Hernandez, 2000-2017 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Flaco Jimenez, 1987-2016 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Steve Jordan, 2009-2011, undated (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Emilio Navaira, 1989-2003 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - Emilio Navaira, 2007-2008 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    - Emilio Navaira, 2009-2010, 2016 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Advertisements and Mounted Material
    - Advertisements. Accordion Dreams film - Hoehner Accordion, 1978, 1989, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 12)
    - Advertisements. KSAB Radio Sabrosa 99.9 FM and Manny Music, Autograph Souvenir - Whole Enchilada Merchandising, 1995-1997, 2001, undated (Map-case 37, Folder 13)
    - Mounted Photographs and Artwork. Little Joe Hernandez (and the Latinaires), 1996, undated (Map-case 38, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Photographs and Artwork. Selena: Mounted photographs, 1985, 1995, undated (Map-case 38, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Photographs and Artwork. Selena: Mounted photographs and artwork, undated (Map-case 39, Folder 1-2)
    - Mounted Male Artist Album Covers. David Lee Garza y Los Musicales featuring Emilio Navaira - Bob Gallarza, 1988, 1993 (Map-case 40, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Female Artist Album Covers. Laura Canales y Carlos Miranda - Lisa Lopez, 1986, undated (Map-case 40, Folder 2)
    - Selena Mounted Album Publicity and Posters (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Map-case 40, Folder 3)
    - Selena Mounted Album Publicity and Posters (2 of 2), 1996, undated (Map-case 41, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Clippings. Little Joe Hernandez - Laura Canales, 1986-2000, undated (Map-case 41, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Clippings. Augie Meyers, 1987, 1992, 2001 (Map-case 42, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Clippings. Selena., 1986, 1989-1990 (Map-case 42, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Clippings. Selena, 1994-1995, undated (Map-case 43, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Clippings. Selena, undated (Map-case 43, Folder 2)
    - Mounted Clippings. Hacienda Records, 1979, 1999, 2004 (Map-case 44, Folder 1)
    - Mounted Event Posters, 1999 (Map-case 44, Folder 2)
- Record Labels, 1950-2016, undated
  Series III: Record Labels, 1950-2016,undated
  Boxes 165-171
  Arranged alphabetically by record label, this series contains promotional material, business documents, and catalogs from prominent Tejano record labels. Hacienda Records is particularly well-represented. Also,of note is correspondence from Carmen Marroquin (of the sister musical act Carmen and Laura) whose husband Armando Marroquin founded Ideal Records.
  - A.C.E. Records Inc., undated (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - AFG Sigma Records, 1995, undated (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - AMS Records, 1988, 1990, undated (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - A.R.C. Discos, 2002, 2004 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - A.R.C. Discos - Audiovisual material, 2006 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Arhoolie Records, undated (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Arhoolie Records - Catalogs, 1978-1997, undated (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Arhoolie Records - Clippings, 1988, 2015, undated (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Arista, 1993-1995, undated (Box 165, Folder 9)
  - Barb Wire, 1996 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Bego Record Co., undated (Box 165, Folder 11)
  - BMG, 1990, 1995, undated (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Cam-Mex Records, undated (Box 165, Folder 13)
  - Canasta Records, undated (Box 165, Folder 14)
  - Capitol/EMI Latin, 1989-1993, undated (Box 165, Folder 15)
  - CARA Records, undated (Box 165, Folder 16)
  - CARA Records - Ramón Hernández material, 1987, undated (Box 165, Folder 17)
  - CARA Records - Clippings, 1989-1990, undated (Box 165, Folder 18)
  - Catalina Records, 2002, undated (Box 165, Folder 19)
  - Catalina Records - Ramón Hernández material, 2002 (Box 165, Folder 20)
  - Colores Records, undated (Box 165, Folder 21)
  - Corona Records, 2007 (Box 165, Folder 22)
  - Crazy Cajun, undated (Box 165, Folder 23)
  - Discos Fuentes, 2001 (Box 165, Folder 24)
  - Discos Supremo, undated (Box 165, Folder 25)
  - Eagle Music Productions, undated (Box 165, Folder 26)
  - EMI Latin - Publicity, 1996-2001, undated (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - EMI Latin - Newsletters (1 of 2), 2000 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - EMI Latin - Newsletters (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - EMI Latin - Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Freddie Records - Photographs, undated (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Freddie Records - Concerts and events, 1994-2001 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Freddie Records - Publicity, 1999-2008, undated (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Freddie Records - Catalogs, undated (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Freddie Records - Ramón Hernández material, 2013, undated (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Freddie Records - Clippings, 200-2011, undated (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Freddie Records - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 166, Folder 11)
  - GIL Records, undated (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - Grupo Central de Discos, undated (Box 166, Folder 13)
  - Hacienda Records - Photographs, undated (Box 166, Folder 14)
  - Hacienda Records - Concert and event publicity, 1999 (Box 166, Folder 15)
  - Hacienda Records - Publicity, 2001, undated (Box 166, Folder 16)
  - Hacienda Records - Catalogs (1 of 2), 1998-2008, undated (Box 166, Folder 17)
  - Hacienda Records - Catalogs (2 of 2), 1998-2008, undated (Box 166, Folder 18)
  - Hacienda Records - Business correspondence and memos, 1996-1999, undated (Box 166, Folder 19)
  - Hacienda Records - Financial records, 1997-2015, undated (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Material - Album production, 1996-1997, undated (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Material - Promotional trips itineraries and reports, undated (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Material - Financial records (1 of 2), 1988-2004, undated (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Hacienda Records -Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Material - Financial records (2 of 2), 1998-1999, undated (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Business records, 1996-2003, undated (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Hacienda Records - Ramón Hernández Business records - Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Hacienda Records - Clippings, 2000-2011, undated (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Hacienda Records - Magazines, 2016 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Hacienda Records - Audiovisual material - CDs, 1999-2006, undated (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Hacienda Records - Audiovisual material - DVDs, 2004-2007, undated (Box 167, Folder 11)
  - Hacienda Records - Promotional material, undated (Box 167, Folder 12)
  - Ideal Records - Photographs, 1950, undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Ideal Records - Catalog, undated (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Ideal Records - Ramón Hernández material, 1987, 2009, undated (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Ideal Records - Clippings, 2007-2011 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - JB Records, undated (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Joey Records, undated (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Joey Records - Concerts and events, 1999 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Joey Records - Publicity, 1998-2000, undated (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Joey Records - Catalogs, 1984-1990 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Joey Records - Clippings, undated (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Joey Records - Magazines (1 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Joey Records - Magazines (2 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Joey Records - Magazines (3 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Joey Records - Audiovisual material, 2006 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Joey Records - Promotional material, undated (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - Joey Records - Branded shopping bags, undated (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Luxor Records, undated (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Manny Music, 1991-2000, undated (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Manny Music - Promotional material, undated (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - MG Records, 2013 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - MKL Records, 2000 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Omega Records, undated (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Q-Zone Records, 2001, undated (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Ramex Records, Inc., undated (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Ritmo Records, 2007 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Roy Sales, Inc., 1995, undated (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Seven Rivers, 2000 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Silva Entertainment, 1997, undated (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Southwest Entertainment Inc., 1995-1996, undated (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Southwest Entertainment Inc. - Catalogs (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - Southwest Entertainment Inc. - Catalogs (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Southwest Wholesale, 1990, 1996, undated (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - Southwest Wholesale - Catalogs, 1996-1997 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Tejano Discos, undated (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Tejano Discos - Publicity, 1992-1994, undated (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Tejano Discos - Catalog, 1993 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Tejano Discos - Design drafts, undated (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Tejas Records, 2000, 2006, undated (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Three Sound Records, undated (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Valmon Records, undated (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Voltage Records, undated (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - El Zarape Recording Company, Inc., undated (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Record Labels - Oversized material, [1989], undated (Box 171)
- Media Outlets, 1964-2014, undated
  Series IV: Media Outlets, 1964-2014, undated Boxes 172-177
  The bulk of the series is radio station press kits and promotional material. There are a small number of TV stations, news outlets, and film production companies also included. The many radio station coverage maps that span all across Texas are unexpected highlights of this series.
  - Radio Stations
    - Amerimex International Media, Inc., 1988 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Amigosradio.com, undated (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Bernal Christian Radio, 2002, undated (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - BNetRadio, undated (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Border Media Partners (BMP), 2006, undated (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Cadena Radio Centro, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - La Campensina Network, 1998, undated (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Contemporary Hispanic Network, undated (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - La Favorita, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Heftel Broadcasting Corporation, 1998, undated (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Hispanic Broadcasting Corporation, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Hispanic Radio Network, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - HotTejano.com, undated (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - KBBA 1470 AM, undated (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - KBBA 1560 AM, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - KBEC 1390, 1989, undated (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - KBLN 910 AM, 1988, undated (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - KBMA 99.5 FM, undated (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - KBNA 920 AM/97.5 FM, 1998, undated (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - KBOO, 1999 (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - KBOP, undated (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - KBOR 1600 AM/ FM 106, undated (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - KBRZ 1460 AM, undated (Box 172, Folder 23)
    - KBSO 94.7 FM, undated (Box 172, Folder 24)
    - KBTS 94.3 FM, undated (Box 172, Folder 25)
    - KBUC 830 AM, 1990, undated (Box 172, Folder 26)
    - KCCT 1150 AM, undated (Box 172, Folder 27)
    - KCOM, undated (Box 172, Folder 28)
    - KCOR 1350 AM, 1988, 2000, undated (Box 172, Folder 29)
    - KCTI 1450 AM / KPJN 106.3, 1992, undated (Box 172, Folder 30)
    - KDSI 1070 AM, 1990, undated (Box 172, Folder 31)
    - KDWT, undated (Box 172, Folder 32)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Photographs, undated (Box 172, Folder 33)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Events, 1988-1992, undated (Box 172, Folder 34)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Weekly charts, 1989-2004 (Box 172, Folder 35)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Marketing, 1982-1988, undated (Box 172, Folder 36)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Press kits, 1980, undated (Box 172, Folder 37)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Clippings, 1980-2014 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Clippings, undated (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - KEDA 1540 AM - Promotional material, undated (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - KEDT 90.3 FM / KVRT 90.7 FM, 1996 (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - KEJS 106.5 FM, 1992-1994 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - KELG 1440 AM, 1989, 1996, undated (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - KELG 1440 AM - Marketing research, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - KENR 1070 AM, 1996-1997, undated (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - KEPG 100.9 FM, 1993, 1996, undated (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - KEPS 1270 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - KESS 1270 AM, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - KEYH 850 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - KEYJ 108 FM, undated (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - KFHM 1160 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - KFHM 1160 AM, 1990, undated (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - KFJZ 870 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - KFNA 1060 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - KFRD 980 AM/105 FM, 1986, undated (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - KFRD 980 AM/105 FM - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - KFST 860 AM / 94.3 FM, undated (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - KGBC 1540 AM, 1993, 1999, undated (Box 173, Folder 21)
    - KGBT 1530 AM, undated (Box 173, Folder 22)
    - KGDD 1520 AM, 2003-2004 (Box 173, Folder 23)
    - KGUL 1560 AM, 1988, 1992, undated (Box 173, Folder 24)
    - KHMC 95.9 FM, 1992, undated (Box 173, Folder 25)
    - KIBL 1490 AM/ 104.9 FM, 1985, undated (Box 173, Folder 26)
    - KICK 99.1 FM, 2000, undated (Box 173, Folder 27)
    - KIKZ 1250 AM / KSEM 106.3, undated (Box 173, Folder 28)
    - KINE, undated (Box 173, Folder 29)
    - KINT 93.9 FM, 1994, undated (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - KIQI 1010 AM, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - KIRT 1580 AM, 1986, undated (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - KITM 105.5 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - KIUN 1400 AM / KPTX 98.3, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - KIWW 96.1 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - KJAC 1490 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - KJBZ 92.7 FM, 1989-1990, undated (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - KJTZ 106.9 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - KKLB 92.5 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - KKPS 99.5 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - KKUP 91.5 FM, 1992, undated (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - KLAR 1300 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - KLAT 1010 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - KLAX 97.9 FM, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - KLBO, undated (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - KLEN 106.3 FM, 1996, 2005 (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - KLEY 94.1 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - KLFB 1420 AM, 1984-1987, undated (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - KLSR 105.3 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - KLTN 93.3 FM, 1992, undated (Box 174, Folder 21)
    - KLTO 1230 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 22)
    - KLVL 1480 AM, 1992-2003, undated (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - KLVO 97.7 FM, 1998, undated (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - KLVT 105.5 FM, undated (Box 174, Folder 25)
    - KMIQ 104.9 FM, 1992, 2010, undated (Box 174, Folder 26)
    - KMJR 98.3 FM, 2013 (Box 174, Folder 27)
    - KMPQ 980 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 28)
    - KMRK 96.1 FM, 1990, undated (Box 174, Folder 29)
    - KMXO 1500 AM, 1988 (Box 174, Folder 30)
    - KNDA 102.9 FM, 1995 (Box 174, Folder 31)
    - KNEZ, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 32)
    - KNON 89.3 FM, 1993, undated (Box 174, Folder 33)
    - KOYL 1310 AM / KCLR 1530 AM, undated (Box 174, Folder 34)
    - KPAN 860 AM/ 106.3 FM, 1989, undated (Box 174, Folder 35)
    - KPAS 103.1 FM, 1988-1989 (Box 174, Folder 36)
    - KPET 690 AM, 1989 (Box 174, Folder 37)
    - KPFT 90.1 FM, 1993, undated (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - KPQZ 100.9 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - KPSO 1260 AM, 1983, 1989, undated (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - KPUR 1440 AM, 1989, undated (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - KQFX 104.3 FM, 1994, 2002, undated (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - KQLM 107.9 FM / KOZA 1230 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - KQQK 106.5 FM / 107.9 FM, 1991, undated (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - KQQK 106.5 FM / 107.9 FM - Audiovisual material, 2002 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - KQQQ 92.1 FM / KQQA 1530 AM, 1998, undated (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - KRDF 99.9 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - KRGT 92.1 FM, 1988 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - KRIA 930 AM, 1988, undated (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - KRIO 94.1 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - KRMY 1050 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - KROB 1510 AM, 2007 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - KRTX 980 AM / 100.7 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - KRVA 1600 AM, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - KRZI 1580 AM, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - KSAB 99.9 FM / KUNO 1400 AM, 1995, 2008 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - KSAH 720 AM, 1986, 2000, undated (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - KSAH 720 AM - Clippings, 1986, 1988, undated (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - KSAH 720 AM - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - KSEY 1230 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - KSJT 107.5 FM, 1985, undated (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - KSPL 1470 AM / 107.1 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 25)
    - KSSA 1600 AM/ 106.9 FM, 1992, undated (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - KSSQ 1140 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 27)
    - KSTA 1000 AM / 107.1 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 28)
    - KSVE 1150 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 29)
    - KTAM 1240 AM, 2001 (Box 175, Folder 30)
    - KTEM 1400 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 31)
    - KTEP 88.5 FM, 1996 (Box 175, Folder 32)
    - KTLK 1460 AM, 1988 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    - KTKO 105.7 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 34)
    - KTLU 103.9 FM /1580 AM / KWRW 97.7, undated (Box 175, Folder 35)
    - KTSB 91.7 FM, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 36)
    - KTXN 98.7 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 37)
    - KTXZ 1560 AM, 1991, undated (Box 175, Folder 38)
    - KTZA 93 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 39)
    - KUKA 105.9 FM, undated (Box 175, Folder 40)
    - KULP 1390 AM, undated (Box 175, Folder 41)
    - KUNO 1400 AM, 1986-1997, undated (Box 175, Folder 42)
    - KUVA 102.3 FM, undated (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - KVIV 1340 AM, undated (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - KVJY 840 AM, undated (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - KVMC 1320 AM, 1993, 2002, undated (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - KVOU 1400 AM / KYUF 105, undated (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - KVOZ 890 AM / KOYE 95 FM, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - KVRP 1400 AM, undated (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - KWBC 1550 AM / KMBV 92.5 FM, undated (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - KWEL 1070 AM, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - KWHW 1450 AM, undated (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - KWTX 1230 AM, 1992-1993, undated (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - KXEB 910 AM, 1990, undated (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - KXET 1250 AM (KVAR 1250 AM), 1984, undated (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - KXEW 1600 AM, 1979 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - KXEX 1550 AM, 1990, 1993, undated (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - KXTJ 107.9 FM, undated (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - KXTN 107.5 FM, 1996, 2000 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - KXTN 107.5 FM - Clippings, 1991-2000, undated (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - KXTN 107.5 FM - Promotional material, 2003, undated (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - KXTQ 950 AM / 93.7 FM, 1988, undated (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - KXYZ 1320 AM, 1991, undated (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - KYMI 107.9 FM, undated (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - KYND 1520 AM, 1997, undated (Box 176, Folder 23)